are you sick of using the exact same
你是否厌倦了
layouts for every hero section of every
每个网站的每个首页都使用完全相同的布局？
website well in this video I'm going to
那么在这段视频中，我将
share with you 18 different hero
与你分享 18 种不同的首页布局
variations that you can steal to start
变体，你可以立即借鉴并
using in your designs today let's get
应用到你的设计中。让我们开始吧！
into it now the first hero layouts that
首先，
I want to cover are those that I would
我要介绍的是我认为非常
classify as all reliable these are
可靠的首页布局。这些
layouts that you're going to see all the
布局你经常会看到，
them all the time it's because they work
它们之所以如此常见，是因为它们
in terms of conversion usability and the
在转化率和用户体验方面都非常有效。
first and probably most common is this
第一种，也是最常见的布局，就是
classic Left Right layout right you've
经典的左右布局。左边是
got your text and your called to action
文字和行动号召，
on the left and the image on the right a
右边是图片。一个
good example of this is this stairs
很好的例子是这个楼梯
website and you can see especially with
网站。你可以看到，尤其是在
a nice graphic on the right side it's
右边添加一张漂亮的图片后，
really going to bring this basic layout
这个基本的布局会变得
to life another thing that you can do is
生动起来。你还可以
take that image on the right side and
将右侧的图片
stretch it to the height of the viewport
拉伸到视口的高度，这样
and by doing this it's going to create a
做可以营造出一种更具
little bit more of a custom feel and I
个性化的感觉。我
really like this example by pheno now
非常喜欢 Pheno 的这个例子。
both of these layouts can be flipped and
这两种布局都可以翻转，
so rather than left right you're going
所以与其…… 左右方向，也就是
right left meaning you have the image on
图片在
the left and you have the text and call
左边，文字和
to action on the right now while this is
行动号召在右边。虽然这种
a nice way to shake it up I don't really
布局方式可以带来一些新鲜感，但我并不
recommend that you use this too often
建议经常使用。
because typically speaking with most
因为大多数
languages we read left to right and
语言的阅读顺序都是从左到右，
that's the way that we look at websites
浏览网站也是如此。所以，如果
as well and so if you've got the image
图片
on the left that's typically going to be
在左边，它通常会是
the first thing that people look at so
人们首先看到的内容。
unless you've got a really powerful
除非你的图片非常有力，能够清晰地
image that conveys your message and your
传达你的信息和
value proposition
价值主张，否则
I wouldn't typically recommend putting
我通常不建议把
your image on the left but there is a
图片放在左边。不过这里有一个
good example of this here they still do
很好的例子，他们仍然
a good job of calling attention to the
成功地吸引了人们对
text on the right side so in this case I
右侧文字的注意力。所以我
feel like it's kind of working the other
觉得这种布局方式效果还不错。
thing that you can do is again bring
你还可以把
that image to the full height of the
图片拉到整个
viewport and here's another great
视口的高度。这里还有一个很好的
example of that all right so the next
例子。接下来
one that I want to talk about is one
我想谈谈一种
that I would classify as old school and
我称之为“老式”的布局方式。
the reason that I classify this as old
之所以说它老式，是因为这种布局方式是
see years ago
几年前才会出现的。
wouldn't really recommend this one but
这种布局会让网站显得过时，所以我不太推荐。
this layout is having the image on the
这种布局是将图片放在
background and then the text as an
背景上，文字作为
overlay over the top now again this can
叠加层放在图片上方。当然，这种布局也可以
be done Tastefully and so I don't want
做得比较雅致，所以我并不是
to say you should never use this but
说你永远不应该使用这种布局，只是
it's really easy to kind of lose track
很容易让人忽略
of the text in the image but one example
图片中的文字。
that I really liked of this is this
我非常喜欢的一个例子是
website secret developers you can see
Secret Developers 这个网站。你可以看到，
they've got a really nice image on the
他们的背景图片非常漂亮，
backdrop but they still are using some
但他们仍然在前面使用了一些
old text over the front um to bring your
文字，以吸引你的
focus to that text the one thing that I
注意力。我
don't like is the call to action is
不喜欢的一点是，行动号召按钮很难被
really difficult to see over the image
图片遮挡住。
all right so now we're going to talk
好了，现在我们要讨论
about centered layouts I am actually a
居中布局。我其实
big fan of centered layouts back in
很喜欢居中布局。
college when I was taking design classes
大学时我上设计课，
my teachers would say you should never
老师总是说千万不要把
Centerline text it's not tasteful it
文字居中，说这样不雅观，不好看。
doesn't look good but honestly I think
但说实话，我觉得居中布局更
it's kind of easy to consume and it
容易阅读，而且
keeps things looking really nice and
能让页面看起来更美观流畅。
flow really nicely and so a few examples
举几个例子，比如
of this are just this Classic Center
这个经典的居中
layout where you've got your text call
布局： 你的文字
to action and then your image and often
号召和图片，通常
times that image is going to kind of
图片会
flow out of the bottom of the viewport
超出视口底部，
but as long as enough of that image or
但只要显示的图片或视频足够多，就能
video is showing it's going to encourage
鼓励
people to scroll to see more and here's
用户滚动查看更多内容。这里有
a great example of this um from this
一个很好的例子，来自这个
website ping the next one is a slight
网站。下一个例子是
variation of this centered layout where
这种居中布局的略微变体，
we're taking the image and bringing it
我们将图片放在了
above the call to action I personally am
号召上方。我个人
not a huge fan of this because we want
不太喜欢这种做法，因为我们希望
to keep that call to action as one of
号召仍然是
the main focal points but there are
主要的视觉焦点之一，但在某些
cases where this can be done Tastefully
情况下，这种做法可以做得非常巧妙。
in this case elter Bank does kind of a
例如，Elter Bank 就采用了一种
cool graphic that comes up and over the
很酷的图形，将其置于
call to action might be something worth
号召上方，这或许值得你
looking into and trying in your designs
借鉴并运用到你的设计中。
the next one that I really like is the
我非常喜欢的下一个例子是
center align text and call to action
居中对齐的文字和号召，并在
with a few images floating around the
两侧添加一些图片。
sides this is a great example here home
这是一个很好的例子，来自 Home
hero where they're actually using um
Hero，他们使用了
different like profile pictures of happy
不同的、例如快乐的
people this kind of conveys their
人的头像，这有效地传达了他们的
message um I'm a big fan of this I'm
信息。我非常喜欢这种做法，甚至
such a big fan of this that I've even
自己也
used it in my own website P Pro you can
用过。 在我的个人网站 P Pro 上，您可以
see that we've got a couple of profile
看到我们设置了一些个人资料
pictures with little like text boxes
图片，图片下方会弹出一些文本框，用来介绍
about our P Pro Community for web
我们的 P Pro 网页
designers I'm a big fan of this and you
设计师社区。我非常喜欢这种方式。您还
can see that I also used a slight
可以看到，我还使用了一种略微
variation where the video our promo
不同的设计，将我们的宣传
video is showing just a little bit on
视频显示在
the bottom of the viewport which is
视口底部，这样可以
encourages people to scroll and watch
引导用户滚动观看。
that video the next ones that I want to
接下来我想
talk about are horizontal variations and
谈谈水平布局，这种布局方式
these are horizontally aligned in terms
在
of the text and call to action I think
文本和行动号召方面都是水平对齐的。我认为
this is a really creative way to lay out
这是一种非常有创意的首页布局方式。
your hero section so you can see here
您可以看到，
we've got the main header to the left
左侧是主标题，右侧是
the subheader and the call to action to
副标题和行动号召，
the right and then the image down below
下方是图片。Spline 就是
a good example of this is spline I
一个很好的例子。我
actually think they do this pretty
认为他们在这方面做得非常
Tastefully they've got some cool imagery
出色，图片也很酷，
um and they have a great use of
而且他们很好地运用了
hierarchy so you know exactly where to
层级结构，让您能够准确地找到想要关注的地方：醒目的
look you've got the big bold header
大标题、
you've got the subtext you've got a
副标题、
colored call to action um they do this
彩色行动号召等等。他们在这方面做得非常
really really well the next one is a
出色。下一个例子是另一种
slight variation of that where you're
略微不同的布局方式。 那种把
actually taking the subtext and moving
副标题移到
this to the left I am not a fan of this
左边的做法，我不太喜欢，
one because again traditionally we're
因为传统上我们是
reading left to right and we don't want
从左到右阅读的，我们不希望
people to read the subtext before they
人们在
read the main text or value proposition
阅读正文或价值主张之前先阅读副标题。
and this kind of goes against basic
这种做法违背了基本的
philosophy of hierarchy because you've
层级原则，因为
got your main header in the middle
中间的主标题
that's bigger so that should call
更大，应该能
people's attention a little bit more but
更吸引人们的注意力，但人们
when they're reading left to right
从左到右阅读时，
they're also prone to read the subtext
也往往会先阅读副标题。
first I just don't think that this is
我觉得这种布局
very user friendly but it might be
不太友好，但或许
something worth trying out the next one
值得一试。下一个例子是在
is a huge um hero image over the top and
顶部放置一张巨大的主图，
then we've got our header and our
然后是标题和副标题。
subheader down below this is kind of an
这是一种很
interesting layout um mainly because in
有意思的布局，主要是因为
the examples that I found they don't
我找到的示例中都没有行动
really have a call to action however
号召。不过，
there are occasionally websites where
有些网站
you don't really need a call to action
确实不需要行动号召，
they're just websites that are built to
它们只是为了
convey information and so this might be
传递信息而构建的。所以，
a layout that you want to use if you
如果你
have a website like that that doesn't
有一个不需要
necessarily have a call to action the
行动号召的网站，这种布局或许值得考虑。
next layout that I want to talk about
接下来我想谈谈我
are those that I classified as Quirky
归类为“另类”的布局。
these are ones that wouldn't necessarily
这些布局不一定
recommend using on an everyday basis but
适合日常使用，但
they might be fun variations to try in
它们或许可以作为一些设计中的有趣变体。
some of your designs the first one
第一个例子
utilizes somewhat of a background image
利用了背景图片，
where you've got the text that slightly
文字略微
overlays the image and then we've got
覆盖在图片上，
our subheader down to the bottom right
副标题则位于右下角。
this is kind of a cool example of that
这是一个很酷的例子。使用
now with this you want to make sure that
这种布局时，你需要确保
header and the image and so you're going
标题和图片之间有足够的对比度，因此在
you choose I also sometimes see
选择颜色时要格外小心。我有时也会看到
variations where the text overlays it
文字覆盖图片的变体，文字
would invert to the color white so again
会反转成白色。
this may not be the easiest to read but
这种布局可能不太容易阅读，但
it is kind of a cool way to shake up
它确实是一种让
your hero section the next example is a
你的首页部分焕然一新的好方法。下一个例子
slight variation from what we've talked
与我们之前讨论的一些例子略有不同，标题居中位于顶部，
you've got an image down below and then
图片位于下方，
you've got your subheader and the call
副标题和
to action in the bottom right I kind of
行动号召按钮则位于右下角。我比较
like this example because you've got a
喜欢这个例子，因为它有一个醒目的
big fat burger in the bottom left but
大标题。 左下角是汉堡包，但
you still are utilizing hierarchy and
你仍然运用了层级结构，
people are going to be able to read kind
人们可以
of left Center to right so this one
从左到右阅读，所以这个设计
actually works pretty well and I kind of
效果很好，我很喜欢。
like this the next example is actually
下一个例子是我非常
one that I'm a big fan of the only thing
喜欢的，唯一
you have to be careful of is making sure
需要注意的是，确保信息量
that this doesn't become too
不要太大。
overwhelming but you've got all of your
所有
important info to the left your text
重要信息都放在左边：文字、
call to action you've got an image in
行动号召，中间是图片，右边是
the center and then you've got some
一些
additional um text or even buttons to
额外的文字，甚至是按钮。
the right and I really like this example
我真的很喜欢这个例子，
of trend you can see that again you're
你可以看到，你
still going to be creating left to right
仍然遵循从左到右的阅读顺序：
big text down to call to action you've
大字到行动号召，
got a really cool image in the center
中间是一张很酷的图片，
but then on the right you actually have
右边是
buttons that are sliders to change that
滑动条按钮，可以切换
image again you want to be careful to
图片。同样，要注意
not overwhelm people with too much in
不要在
your hero section but this is a cool
首页区域放置太多信息，以免让人眼花缭乱。这是一个很棒的
variation that I would definitely
变体，我强烈
recommend trying out in your designs the
建议你在设计中尝试一下。
next example is again just a slight
下一个例子和
change up from the ones we just spoke
我们刚才讨论的略有不同，我们
about but we've got our text and then
有文字，然后是
our call to action kind of slanting to
行动号召……
the right starting from the center
从中心向右倾斜，
and then we've got images on the left
左侧是图片。
again you want to be careful using your
再次强调，在左侧使用图片要谨慎，
images on the left just because that's
因为
what people are probably going to see
人们很可能
first but there are ways to do this
首先看到的是图片，但也有办法
Tastefully it's showing these books on
巧妙地运用。这里展示的是
the left which I actually think in this
左侧的书籍，我认为这种做法非常
case it really works because it's
有效，因为它
showing some of what they're offering
展示了他们提供的部分产品，
and so I actually like this and then
所以我很喜欢。
their call to action the bottom right is
右下角的行动号召是
a search bar rather than a button which
一个搜索栏而不是按钮，这同样
again depending on the purpose of your
取决于网站的用途，有时效果
website can work really well the next
会非常好。接下来
one that I'm actually a huge fan of is
我非常喜欢的是
this slight centered variation but
一种略微居中的变体，但与居中布局不同的是，这里将
you've got your subtext and call to
副标题和
action on a horizontal alignment and
行动号召放在水平位置，
then you've got images to the left and
图片分别位于左右两侧。
to the right this website puzzle is a
这个网站拼图就是一个
really cool example of this the images
很好的例子，图片
are not necessarily descriptive but they
不一定具有描述性，但它们
are on brand and they're really bright
符合品牌调性，而且
and color colorful and fun and then I
色彩鲜艳、趣味十足。我
also like that they're calling more
还喜欢他们
attention to the call to action with the
用
little arrow so this is a really cool
小箭头来突出行动号召。这是一个非常棒的
variation that I'm definitely going to
变体，我肯定会继续使用。
be using the next one is a variation
接下来要介绍的这种布局
that I'm not super thrilled about but
我不太喜欢，但
they are somewhat sticking to the whole
它基本遵循了
idea of header to the left and then
左侧标题、右侧内容的布局理念。
moving to the right the only problem is
唯一的问题是
the header is in the bottom left and
标题位于左下角，而
in the center kind of slanting down you
中间的大图则略微向下倾斜，就像
can see in this example here the reason
这个例子里展示的那样。这种布局之所以有效，
that this one is working is because
是因为
those images are portraying what it is
这些图片清晰地展示了
that they offer what they do it's it's
他们提供的服务内容，也就是
the the UI of their app but again this
他们的应用程序用户界面。但这种布局
can get a little confusing when people
可能会让用户感到困惑：
are looking they're going to start at
他们会先从
the top left and then go to the bottom
左上角开始，然后移到左下角阅读标题，接着移到中间
going to go to the center to see the
查看
images and then top right to read the
图片，再移到右上角阅读副标题，最后才会发现行动
where the call to action is and they're
号召按钮在哪里，然后又会移到
going to go to the bottom right and so
右下角。所以，这种布局
it can get kind of overwhelming but it
可能会让人感到不知所措。不过，这
might be something worth trying out the
或许值得一试。
next variation this is something that I
接下来要介绍的这种布局我
have really loved and I'm seeing this
非常喜欢，而且现在也
more often and this is using a standard
越来越常见。它采用的是标准
layout but instead of having imagery in
布局，但图片的位置与
a traditional location like Left Right
传统的布局不同。 左、右、
Center they've got it within the header
中，他们把图片放在了页眉里，
and this is a really fun way to express
这是一种非常有趣的方式，可以
more in the main H1 of your website and
在网站的主要 H1 标签中表达更多信息。
like they say a picture is worth a
正如人们常说的，一张图片胜过
thousand words and so if you're trying
千言万语，所以如果你想
to say more in the main text of your
在首页的“
hero section this might be the variation
英雄”部分用文字表达更多内容，这或许是个不错的选择。
for you and I really like this example
我真的很喜欢这个例子，
you can see they've got different images
你可以看到他们在创意机构的海洋主题图片上使用了不同的图片。
I'm obsessed with this layout it is a
我非常喜欢这种布局，它有点
little bit more quirky a little bit more
古怪，有点另类，
out there but if you do it in a a very
但如果你以一种非常
conservative way I think it can work
保守的方式使用，我认为它也能取得很好的效果。
really well now if you like this video
如果你喜欢这个视频，
hit the like button and subscribe to my
请点赞并订阅我的
channel if you haven't already because
频道（如果你还没有订阅的话），因为
I've got new videos just like this one
我每周都会发布像这样的新视频。
coming out every single week plus if
此外，如果
you're interested in applying for our
你有兴趣申请加入我们的
private Community for web designers
网页设计师专属社区，我们
where we have monthly trainings we share
每月都会举办培训、分享
resources and we have monthly design
资源，还有每月一次的设计
competitions with huge cash prizes be
比赛，奖金丰厚，请
sure to click the link down below or you
点击下面的链接或
can go to ppro do.com to apply I hope to
访问 ppro do.com 申请。希望能在社区里
see you inside and we'll catch you in
见到你，我们
the next video
下个视频见！